Gideon Kimeli

Kenya



gideonkimelikoech@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/gideon-kimeli-1bb072187

Summary

I am a senior freelance research writer with five years working experience as a content writer, academic writing/ specialist. I have written close to 3000 projects for different clients across the globe and in different levels of complexity. So, be assured of quality services from me.

Experience



senior freelance research writer/academic specialist

Www.Allwriting.Net Jan 2013 - Oct 2016 (3 years 10 months) Doing freelance research writing services

p freelance research writer

Upwork Jan 2017 - Present (5 years 6 months +) freelance research writing services

Education



Moi University

Bachelor's degree, Lands survey 2017 - 2021 Lands survey and mapping

Skills

Content Marketing • Creative Writing • Writing • Business Management • English • Literature Reviews